Fallout 76 is the second lowest Triple-A
rated game of all time.
After uhhhh...
Misunderstood Masterpiece.
So it's actually the lowest rated game of all time.
How...could this happen?
Well...
It was intentional.
I've seen people online call it a quick cash grab...
But that doesn't make any sense.
...because it's terrible at grabbing cash.
So...there had to be another reason why
it's so mediocre.
The problem was, I would have to play the
game to find out why.
I didn't want to spend money on something that's supposed to be bad, so..
...so I decided to rob a GameStop.
As, uh, when I entered the store...
...they pulled a gun on me...
...and told me to take a copy from them or die.
(rage surpressed)
After downloading my physical copy...
...and playing the game for five hours.
My first thought was...
You know Viking Funerals?
Setting the ship on fire?
I thought this might be a
Viking Funeral for their engine.
Nope.
Because they will use it for both Starfield and Skyrim 2...
...and then probably for another 50 years.
I had to play on...
...and after another 10 hours...
I was 90% sure (that) this is an art piece.
A Todd Original.™
If you look at the way critics are describing it...
These are all positive things when describing artwork.
So it made perfect sense.
But there was one big problem...
Art Games don't make any money...
...and this game was EXTREMELY expensive to make.
They said this is
"The largest project they've ever done."
You might doubt that.
But Todd has never lied before.
So sadly, it can't be art.
Because there's no money in it.
And making serious motherfucking
money is the whole point...
...of Capitalism.
That's when it clicked...
It was so obvious with the Food Meter.
Fallout 76 is a political statement.
Bethesda is trying to make the point that the player...
...needs a governing system where the
NPCs are in control.
But you, a player, can influence their control.
By electing who to help, or choosing who
you want to trade with.
This world where everyone shares everything...
...and everyone starts equally...
...is broken.
All the wanderers uniting to take
down the evil queen...
...it doesn't work.
What Bethesda is saying is that Fallout 76's system...
...IS THE VERY DEFINITION OF FAILURE.
COMMUNISTS DETECTED ON AMERICAN SOIL.
LETHAL FORCE ENGAGED.
AMERICA WILL NEVER FALL TO
COMMUNIST INVASION.
HONORING THE FALLEN IS THE DUTY OF EVERY RED-BLOODED AMERICAN. This video was subtitled by san7890\!l (Partail edits by First Order Ball).